Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Records 5149
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Run Arounds rule #39, Page 74Pay For (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Reprimands (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Trainmen Re-Instated (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Letters from Sup't Trainmaster & General Yard Master (GYM) (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Correspondence from W.G. Innis (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Lunch Period Yard Men (Box 40, Folder 13)
- Seniority-Matters (Box 40, Folder 14)
- Circulars & Letters from W.P. Kennedy (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Investigations (Box 40, Folder 16)
- Communications (Box 40, Folder 17)
- PSF State Legislative Board: Alabama, Pt. 1 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- PSF State Legislative Board: Alabama, Pt. 2 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- PSF State Legislative Board: Alabama, Pt. 3 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- PSF State Legislative Board: Alabama, Pt. 4 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- PSF State Legislative Board: Arkansas, Pt. 1 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- PSF State Legislative Board: Arkansas, Pt. 2 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- PSF State Legislative Board: Arkansas, Pt. 3 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- PSF State Legislative Board: Arizona, Pt. 1 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- PSF State Legislative Board: Arizona, Pt. 2 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- PSF State Legislative Board: California, Pt. 1 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- PSF State Legislative Board: California, Pt. 2 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- PSF State Legislative Board: California, Pt. 3 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- PSF State Legislative Board: California, Pt. 4 (Box 41, Folder 13)
- PSF State Legislative Board: California, Pt. 5 (Box 41, Folder 14)
- PSF State Legislative Board: Colorado, Pt. 1 (Box 41, Folder 15)
- PSF State Legislative Board: Colorado, Pt. 2 (Box 41, Folder 16)
- PSF State Legislative Board: Colorado, Pt. 3 (Box 41, Folder 17)
- PSF State Legislative Board: Colorado, Pt. 4 (Box 41, Folder 18)
- PSF State Legislative Board: Colorado, Pt. 5 (Box 41, Folder 19)
- PSF State Legislative Board: Colorado, Pt. 6 (Box 41, Folder 20)
- PSF State Legislative Board: Connecticut, Pt. 1 (Box 41, Folder 21)
- PSF State Legislative Board: Connecticut, Pt. 2 (Box 41, Folder 22)
- PSF State Legislative Board: Delaware, Pt. 1 (Box 41, Folder 23)
- PSF State Legislative Board: Delaware, Pt. 2 (Box 41, Folder 24)
- PSF State Legislative Board: District of Columbia (Box 41, Folder 25)
- PSF State Legislative Board: Florida, Pt. 1 (Box 41, Folder 26)
- PSF State Legislative Board: Florida, Pt. 2 (Box 41, Folder 27)
- ICC FD 22500-22595, Pt. 1 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  Not part of the container series. Most likely forgotten when ICC FD's were moved to Boxes 7-14.
- ICC FD 22500-22595, Pt. 2 (Box 41, Folder 29)
- ICC FD 22500-22595, Pt. 3 (Box 41, Folder 30)
- ICC FD 22500-22595, Pt. 4 (Box 41, Folder 31)
- ICC FD 22500-22595, Pt. 5 (Box 41, Folder 32)
- ICC FD 22500-22595, Pt. 6 (Box 41, Folder 33)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Georgia, Pt. 1 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Georgia, Pt. 2 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Idaho, Pt. 1 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Idaho, Pt. 2 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Idaho, Pt. 3 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Illinois, Pt. 1 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Illinois, Pt. 2 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Illinois, Pt. 3 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Illinois, Pt. 4 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Illinois, Pt. 5 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Indiana, Pt. 1 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Indiana, Pt. 2 (Box 42, Folder 12)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Indiana, Pt. 3 (Box 42, Folder 13)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Iowa, Pt. 1 (Box 42, Folder 14)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Iowa, Pt. 2 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Iowa, Pt. 3 (Box 42, Folder 16)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Kansas, Pt. 1 (Box 42, Folder 17)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Kansas, Pt. 2 (Box 42, Folder 18)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Kansas, Pt. 3 (Box 42, Folder 19)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Kentucky, Pt. 1 (Box 42, Folder 20)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Kentucky, Pt. 2 (Box 42, Folder 21)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Kentucky, Pt. 3 (Box 42, Folder 22)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Louisiana, Pt. 1 (Box 42, Folder 23)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Louisiana, Pt. 2 (Box 42, Folder 24)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Louisiana, Pt. 3 (Box 42, Folder 25)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Maine, Pt. 1 (Box 42, Folder 26)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Maine, Pt. 2 (Box 42, Folder 27)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Maryland, Pt. 1 (Box 42, Folder 28)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Maryland, Pt. 2 (Box 42, Folder 29)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Maryland, Pt. 3 (Box 42, Folder 30)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Massachusetts, Pt. 1 (Box 42, Folder 31)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Massachusetts, Pt. 2 (Box 42, Folder 32)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Michigan, Pt. 1 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Michigan, Pt. 2 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Michigan, Pt. 3 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Minnesota, Pt. 1 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Minnesota, Pt. 2 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Mississippi, Pt. 1 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Mississippi, Pt. 2 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Missouri, Pt. 1 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Missouri, Pt. 2 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Missouri, Pt. 3 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Missouri, Pt. 4 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Montana, Pt. 1 (Box 43, Folder 12)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Montana, Pt. 2 (Box 43, Folder 13)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Nebraska, Pt. 1 (Box 43, Folder 14)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Nebraska, Pt. 2 (Box 43, Folder 15)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Nebraska, Pt. 3 (Box 43, Folder 16)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Nevada, Pt. 1 (Box 43, Folder 17)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Nevada, Pt. 2 (Box 43, Folder 18)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: New Hampshire, Pt. 1 (Box 43, Folder 19)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: New Hampshire, Pt. 2 (Box 43, Folder 20)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: New Jersey, Pt. 1 (Box 43, Folder 21)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: New Jersey, Pt. 2 (Box 43, Folder 22)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: New Jersey, Pt. 3 (Box 43, Folder 23)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: New Jersey, Pt. 4 (Box 43, Folder 24)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: New Mexico, Pt. 1 (Box 43, Folder 25)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: New Mexico, Pt. 2 (Box 43, Folder 26)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: New York State, Pt. 1 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: New York State, Pt. 2 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: New York State, Pt. 3 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: New York State, Pt. 4 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: New York State, Pt. 5 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: North Carolina, Pt. 1 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: North Carolina, Pt. 2 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: North Dakota, Pt. 1 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: North Dakota, Pt. 2 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Ohio, Pt. 1 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Ohio, Pt. 2 (Box 44, Folder 11)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Ohio, Pt. 3 (Box 44, Folder 12)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Oklahoma, Pt. 1 (Box 44, Folder 13)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Oklahoma, Pt. 2 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Oregon, Pt. 1 (Box 44, Folder 15)
- PSF State Legislative Boards: Oregon, Pt. 2 (Box 44, Folder 16)
- Aldene Plan- New York & New Jersey, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Assessments, 1954-1963 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Association of American Railroads, 1962-1964 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Association of American Railroads, Pt. 2, 1966-1967 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Away-From-Home Expenses Deductible From Income Tax (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Brandon & Shearer (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Brandon, Shearer & Flaherty, 1964-1965 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Bills, 1965 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Bills, Pt. 2, 1965 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Bills, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Bills-1967 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Bills- 1967 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Chase, W.E.B. (General Secretary.-Treas.) (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Bureau of Occupation & Per Capita Tax (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Chesser, A.H. (Nat'l. Legis. Rep.), 1962-1963 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Chesser, A. H. (Nat'l. Legis. Rep.) (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Circular of Instructions, Pt. 1, 1962-1965 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Circular of Instructions, Pt. 2, 1962-1965 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Circular of Instructions, Pt. 3, 1962-1965 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Circular of Instructions, Pt. 4 (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Contingency Fund (Box 46, Folder 11)
- Co-Operative Legislative Committee (Box 47, Folder 1)
- COPE (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Dannecker, H.S. 1962-1964 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Dannecker, H.S. 1962-1965 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Dannecker, H.S. 1962-1965 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Dannecker, H.S. 1962-1964 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Dannecker, H.S. 1965-1967 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Dannecker, H.S. 1962-1965 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Danneker [sic], H.S. 1965-1967 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Danneker [sic], H.S. 1964 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Dannecker, H.S. 1964 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Dannecker, H.S. (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Dannecker, H.S. (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Diversion of Mail Traffic from Railroad to Highway Service, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Primary Election (1964 Congress) (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Primary Election- 1964 (Congress) (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Primary Election- 1964 (General Correspondence) (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Primary Election- 1964 (Endorsements) (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Primary Election- 1964 (Endorsements and Answers) (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Democratic National Convention- 1964 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Democratic National Convention- 1964 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- General Elections- 1964: (General Correspondence) (Box 50, Folder 1)
- General Election- 1964 (General Correspondence) (Box 50, Folder 2)
- General Election- 1964 (Endorsements) (Box 50, Folder 3)
- General Election- 1964 (Endorsement Letters and Answers) (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Barry Goldwater (Candidate for President-1964) (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Primary- General- 1965 (General Correspondence) (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Primary- General - 1965 (General Correspondence) (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Primary Election- 1966 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Primary Elections- 1966 (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Primary Election- 1966 (Congressional Endorsements) (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Primary Election- 1966 (Endorsements) (Box 51, Folder 4)
- Primary Election- 1966 (Endorsements Letters and Answers) (Box 51, Folder 5)
- General Election- 1966 (Box 51, Folder 6)
- General Election- 1966 (Box 51, Folder 7)
- General Election- 1966 (Box 51, Folder 8)
- General Election- 1966 (Congressional Endorsements) (Box 52, Folder 1)
- General Election- 1966 (Endorsements) (Box 52, Folder 2)
- General Election- 1966 (Endorsement Letters and Answers) (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Primary Election- 1967 (General Correspondence) (Box 52, Folder 4)
- General Election- 1967 (General Correspondence) (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Primary Election- 1968 (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Congressional Endorsements- 1968 (Primary Election) (Box 52, Folder 7)
- Primary Election- 1968 (Endorsement Letters and Answers) (Box 52, Folder 8)
- Democratic National Convention: Chicago- 1968 (Box 52, Folder 9)
- General Election- 1968 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- General Election- 1968 (Endorsement Letters and Answers) (Box 53, Folder 2)
- General Election- 1968 (Endorsement Letters and Answers) (Box 53, Folder 3)
- General Election: Endorsement Letters and Answers (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Presidential Election- 1968 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- "Letter from Alabama" - George Wallace, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 6)
- Employment of the Handicapped, 1959-1964 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- Employment of the Handicapped, 1959-1964 (Box 54, Folder 2)
- Epistles of W.L. reed (Box 54, Folder 3)
- "Featherbedding" (Box 54, Folder 4)
- Featherbedding- Loomis & Kennedy` (Box 54, Folder 5)
- Federal Employers Liability Act, 1959-1962 (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Federationist Magazine, 1962 (Box 55, Folder 2)
- "F.E.P.C.", 1956-1961 (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Five-Day Work-Week Rules, 1951 (Box 55, Folder 4)
- Flagging P-7: Erie Lackawanna RR, 1964-1965 (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Flagging P-7: New York Central RR (Box 55, Folder 6)
- Flagging P-7: New York Central-RR, 1964-1965 (Box 55, Folder 7)
- Flagging: Ready Company, 1958-1963 (Box 55, Folder 8)
- Flagging: Various Railroads (Box 55, Folder 9)
- Flagging, 1958-1963 (Box 55, Folder 10)
- Flagging: Various Railroads (Box 56, Folder 1)
- Flagging: Various Railroads P-7 (Box 56, Folder 2)
- Flagging: Various Railroads, 1965 (Box 56, Folder 3)
- Flagging: Various Railroads: July 1965-December 1965 (Box 56, Folder 4)
- Flagging: Various Railroads (Box 56, Folder 5)
  July 1965-December 1965
- Flagging: Various Railroads- 1966 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Flagging: Various Railroads- 1966 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Flagging: Various Railroads- 1966 (Box 57, Folder 3)
- Flagging: Various Railroads- 1967 (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Flagging P-7-1 Various Railroads (Box 57, Folder 5)
- Flagging- Rule Books (Various Railroads) (Box 58, Folder 1)
- Rule 99 Flagging (1961) (Box 58, Folder 2)
- Flagging P-7 Rule 99 (Box 58, Folder 3)
- Full Crew Law: January and February 1937 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- Full Crew Law: Jan. to Feb. 1937 (Box 59, Folder 2)
- Full Crew: June and July, 1937 (Box 59, Folder 3)
- 1937 Full Crew Jan. to Mar. (Box 59, Folder 4)
- Full Crew Bill Jan. 1937-1940 (Box 59, Folder 5)
- Full Crew Bill: Jan. 1937-1940 (Box 59, Folder 6)
- Full Crew Information for Injunction Hearing, 1937-1946 (Box 59, Folder 7)
- Full Crew Information for Injunction Hearing, 1937-1946 (Box 59, Folder 8)
- Full Crew: 1950-1954 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Full Crew Law: 1937-1961 (Box 60, Folder 2)
- Amend to Full Crew Law Session, 1951 (Box 60, Folder 3)
- Full Crew (General Letters) (Box 60, Folder 4)
- Full Crew Law- Violations of, 1956-1958 (Box 60, Folder 5)
- Full Crew (Orders) (Box 60, Folder 6)
- Full Crew and Five Per Cent Case (Box 60, Folder 7)
- Full-Crew, 1954-1957 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- Full Crew Consent Decree (Box 61, Folder 2)
- Full Crew 1954-1957 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- Full Crew Consent Decree- 1937-1958 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- Full Crew (Past Correspondence- Since Beginning of the "Full Crew"), 1911-1958 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Full Crew (Past Correspondence- Since Beginning of the "Full Crew"), Pt. 2 (Box 62, Folder 2)
- Full Crew (Past Correspondence Since Beginning of the Full Crew, 1911-1958 (Box 63, Folder 1)
- Full Crew (Past Correspondence Since Beginning of the Full Crew), 1911-1958 (Box 63, Folder 2)
- Full Crew Switching File, 1951 (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Full Crew 1951 (Box 64, Folder 2)
- Minimum Crew Law, Mandatory Flag Law (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Special Bill- House Bill 800 Minimum Full (Box 64, Folder 4)
- Minimum Crew Material (Union R.R. & Editorial in connection with our Minimum Crew Bill) (Box 64, Folder 5)
- G's Miscellaneous (Box 65, Folder 1)
- Grand Lodge (Assessments), 1948-1953 (Box 65, Folder 2)
- Grand Lodge Assessments, 1964-1965 (Box 65, Folder 3)
- Grand Lodge (Increase in Legis. Assessments), 1948-1954 (Box 65, Folder 4)
- Legislative Assessments- Increase (Box 65, Folder 5)
- Grand Lodge (Monthly Report), 1951-1955 (Box 65, Folder 6)
- Grand Lodge (Monthly report) 1951-1955 (Box 65, Folder 7)
- Monthly Report, 1964-1965 (Box 65, Folder 8)
- Monthly Report: Gen Secretary & Treasurer, 1966-1968 (Box 65, Folder 9)
- H's- Miscellaneous, 1960-1966 (Box 65, Folder 10)
- Health and Welfare Plan, 1964-1967 (Box 65, Folder 11)
- Health and Welfare Plan, 1964-1967 (Box 65, Folder 12)
- Industrial & Occupational Safety Conference- 1965 (Box 66, Folder 1)
- Industrial & Occupational Safety Conference- 1966 (Box 66, Folder 2)
- Industrial & Occupational Safety Conference- 1967 (Box 66, Folder 3)
- Increases in Per Diem and Travel Expense, 1964-1965 (Box 66, Folder 4)
- Insurance- B.R.T., 1959-1966 (Box 66, Folder 5)
- Insurance- B.R.T., 1959-1967 (Box 66, Folder 6)
- Internal Affairs, Dept. of, 1963-1967 (Box 66, Folder 7)
- Job Benefit Fund- B.R.T., 1963 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- Kennedy W.P. (President) 1960-1962 (Box 67, Folder 2)
- Kennedy W.P (President) 1960-1962 (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Kennedy W.P. (President) 1960-1962 (Box 67, Folder 4)
- Labor and Industry, Dept. of, 1961-1967 (Box 68, Folder 1)
- Labor & Industry, Dept. of, 1960 (Box 68, Folder 2)
- Lawrence, David L. (Governor), 1959-1962 (Box 68, Folder 3)
- Legal Aid, 1964 (Box 68, Folder 4)
- Meeting General Assembly, 1951 (Box 68, Folder 5)
- Meeting General Assembly, 1951 (Box 68, Folder 6)
- Meeting General Assembly 1951 (Box 68, Folder 7)
- Bills-1953 (Box 69, Folder 1)
- Harry See- Legislation, 1953 (Box 69, Folder 2)
- Harry See- Legislation 1953 (Box 69, Folder 3)
- Bills 1953, 1954-1955 (Box 69, Folder 4)
- Bulletins- 1955 (Box 69, Folder 5)
- General File, 1954-1955 (Box 69, Folder 6)
- General File, 1954-1955 (Box 69, Folder 7)
- Bills 1955 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Legislation- 1955 (Box 70, Folder 2)
- General 1957 (Box 70, Folder 3)
- Legislation- 1957 (Box 70, Folder 4)
- Bulletins- 1957 (Box 70, Folder 5)
- Legislation- 1958 (Box 70, Folder 6)
- Bulletins- 1959 (Box 70, Folder 7)
- General 1959 (Box 70, Folder 8)
- General 1959 (Box 70, Folder 9)
- Legislation- 1959 (Box 71, Folder 1)
- Legislation- 1959 (Box 71, Folder 2)
- Legislation- 1960 (Box 71, Folder 3)
- Bulletins- 1961 (Box 71, Folder 4)
- General- 1961-1962 (Box 71, Folder 5)
- General 1961-1962 (Box 71, Folder 6)
- Legislation- 1961 (Box 71, Folder 7)
- Bulletins, 1963 (Box 72, Folder 1)
- Senate Bulletins, 1963 (Box 72, Folder 2)
- Legislation- 1963 (Box 72, Folder 3)
- Briefing of Bills- House, 1963 (Box 72, Folder 4)
- Briefing of Bills- Senate (Box 72, Folder 5)
- Legislation- 1962 (Box 72, Folder 6)
- General, 1963-1964 (Box 73, Folder 1)
- Legislation, 1964 (Box 73, Folder 2)
- Meeting- September 1, 1965 (Box 73, Folder 3)
- General 1965-1966 (Box 73, Folder 4)
- General 65-66 (Box 73, Folder 5)
- General 1965-1966 (Box 73, Folder 6)
- Legislation 1965 & 1966 (Box 74, Folder 1)
- 1967 AFL-CIO Legislative Program (Box 74, Folder 2)
- General Legislation- 1967 (Box 74, Folder 3)
- General Legislation 1967 (Box 74, Folder 4)
- Legislation 1966 (Box 74, Folder 5)
- Legislation- 1967 (Box 74, Folder 6)
- Legislation- 1968 (Box 74, Folder 7)
- Absentee Voting, 1951 (Box 75, Folder 1)
- Anti-Labor Bills: House Bills 769, 770, 771, and 772 (Box 75, Folder 2)
- Clean Steams Legislation (Box 75, Folder 3)
- Pennsylvania League for Consumer Protection (Box 75, Folder 4)
- Special House Bills 338-648 (Box 75, Folder 5)
- Special House Bills 192, 540 (Box 75, Folder 6)
- Flag Protection (Box 75, Folder 7)
- Compulsory Flag Law (Box 75, Folder 8)
- Law- General Safety (Box 75, Folder 9)
- H.B. 25- Goldstein Bill (Box 75, Folder 10)
- Law- Interstate Commerce Commission (General Rules of Practice), 1956 (Box 76, Folder 1)
- Special House Bill 676 (Box 76, Folder 2)
- Medicare Legislation, 1965 (Box 76, Folder 3)
- House Bill 148 Penal Code 1169 (Box 76, Folder 4)
- Special House Bill 234 (Box 76, Folder 5)
- Special Senate Bill 28 (Box 76, Folder 6)
- Special House Bill 843 (Box 76, Folder 7)
- Special House Bill 691 (Box 76, Folder 8)
- Special House Bill 710 (Box 76, Folder 9)
- Public Utility Act, 1957 (Box 76, Folder 10)
- Law- Public Utility (Box 76, Folder 11)
- Special House Bill 189 (Box 76, Folder 12)
- Law- Crossings (P.U.C.) (Obstructing Public & Private) (Box 76, Folder 13)
- Railroad Bills, 1956-1957 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  Senate Bills 178, 179, 180, 195, 196, 197. House Bills 884, 900, 1070, 1182, 1214, 1501.
- Railroad Bills, 1959 (Box 76, Folder 15)
- Railroad Bills, 1961 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  Originals- to be introduced
- Railroad Bills, 1961-1963 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  House Bills 362, 363, 369, 372, 382, 405
- Railroad Bills- Originals to be Introduced, 1965 (Box 77, Folder 3)
- Railroad Bills, 1961-1963 (Box 77, Folder 4)
- Railroad Bills, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  House Bills 377, 382, 391, 435, 448
- Railroad Bills (Box 77, Folder 6)
  House Bills 634, 638, 639, 702, 730
- Railroad Bills- Originals to be Introduced, 1967 (Box 77, Folder 7)
- Amendment to Criminal Law Relative to R.R. Strikes, 1951-1955 (Box 77, Folder 8)
- Rail Track Motor Cars- Windshield Wipers, Headlights, etc., 1953 (Box 77, Folder 9)
- Reapportionment, 1963 (Box 78, Folder 1)
- Special Session- Nov. 12, 1963 General (Reapportionment) (Box 78, Folder 2)
- Special House Bill 908-909 (Box 78, Folder 3)
- Sales Tax, 1957 (Box 78, Folder 4)
- Sales Tax, 1959 (Box 78, Folder 5)
- Sanders on Buses, 1952-1953 (Box 78, Folder 6)
- School Bus Transportation Bills, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 7)
- Resolution: School for Strike Breakers, 1965-1967 (Box 78, Folder 8)
- Resolution- School for Strike Breakers, 1965-1967 (Box 78, Folder 9)
- S. 3778- Smathers Bill, 1959 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  HR 4742
- H.R. 706 - Establishment of Special boards of Adjustment on Individual Railroads (Box 79, Folder 2)
- Law- Special Railroad Cases (State & Fed) (Box 79, Folder 3)
- H.B. 840 State Income Tax, 1951 (Box 79, Folder 4)
- Special House Bill 526, 1953 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  Installation of telephones on passenger trains
- Time Off for Voting (Box 79, Folder 6)
- Truck Bills- S.B. 744, 1957 (Box 79, Folder 7)
- Unemployment Compensation (Box 79, Folder 8)
- Unemployment Compensation, 1956-1961 (Box 79, Folder 9)
- Unemployment- Compensation, 1963-1964 (Box 80, Folder 1)
- Unemployment Compensation, 1963-1964 (Box 80, Folder 2)
- Unemployment Compensation, 1963-1964 (Box 80, Folder 3)
- Unemployment Compensation, 1965-1966 (Box 81, Folder 1)
- Unemployment Compensation, 1965-1966 (Box 81, Folder 2)
- Regulating Time & Payment of Wages & Earnings, 1954-1956 (Box 81, Folder 3)
- Law- Compensation (Box 81, Folder 4)
- Workmen's Compensation and Occupational Disease Act- 1965 (Box 81, Folder 5)
- Lodge #42- Harrisburg, PA, 1956-1965 (Box 82, Folder 1)
- Harrisburg, 1966-1968 (Box 82, Folder 2)
- Lodge #43- Sunbury, PA, 1956 (Box 82, Folder 3)
- Sunbury, 1967 (Box 82, Folder 4)
- Youngwood (Box 82, Folder 5)
- Lodge #85- Easton, PA, 1961 (Box 82, Folder 6)
- Easton, 1967-1968 (Box 82, Folder 7)
- Lodge #94- Carbondale, PA, 1954-1965 (Box 82, Folder 8)
- Carbondale, 1967 (Box 82, Folder 9)
- Scranton, 1968 (Box 82, Folder 10)
- Lodge #100- Jim Thorpe, Pa., 1958 (Box 82, Folder 11)
- Lodge #105- Oil City, Pa., 1958-1962 (Box 82, Folder 12)
- Lodge #117- Columbia, Pa., 1958-1965 (Box 82, Folder 13)
- Oil City, 1966-1968 (Box 82, Folder 14)
- Columbia, 1967-1968 (Box 82, Folder 15)
- Lodge #95- Scranton, Pa., 1958-1962 (Box 82, Folder 16)
- Lodge #121- Harrisburg, Pa., 1959-1960 (Box 82, Folder 17)
- 127 Harrisburg, 1967-1968 (Box 82, Folder 18)
- Lodge #131: Philadelphia, Pa., 1952-1964 (Box 82, Folder 19)
- 131 Philadelphia, 1968 (Box 82, Folder 20)
- Lodge #142- Meadville, Pa. (Box 83, Folder 1)
- Meadville, 1966-1968 (Box 83, Folder 2)
- Lodge #153- Wilkes-Barre, Pa. (Box 83, Folder 3)
- 153 Wilkes-Barre, 1966-1967 (Box 83, Folder 4)
- Lodge #154- Ashley, Pa. (Box 83, Folder 5)
- 154 Ashley, 1967-1968 (Box 83, Folder 6)
- Lodge #160- Philadelphia, Pa. (Box 83, Folder 7)
- 160 Philadelphia (Box 83, Folder 8)
- Lodge #172- Reading, Pa. (Box 83, Folder 9)
- 172 Reading, 1966-1968 (Box 83, Folder 10)
- 173 Hazleton, 1967-1968 (Box 83, Folder 11)
- Lodge #174- Altoona, Pa. (Box 83, Folder 12)
- 174 Altoona, 1966-1968 (Box 83, Folder 13)
- Lodge #184- Susquehanna, Pa., 1957-1965 (Box 83, Folder 14)
- Lodge #189- Duryea, Pa. (Box 83, Folder 15)
- 189 Pittston, 1967-1968 (Box 83, Folder 16)
- Lodge #199- Erie, Pa. (Box 83, Folder 17)
- 199 Erie, 1967-1968 (Box 83, Folder 18)